hpieurope.com 2017-05-30

# Privacy Policy - HPI Racing

We at HPI Racing take your privacy seriously and have therefore outlined outline how and when we store information about you while you visit our website.

## Information Collected by HPI Racing

We only collect information which is used to improve the features and content of the site. Information collected is never provided to third parties unless required to do so by law.

## Information you provide to us

  * We store your profile details for MYhpi - this may include your home address and the kits and parts you own. This is to enhance your experience with MYhpi and provide better support for the product you own.
  * We store your email address for any new kits you register an interest in receiving updates about. We will only use this to send you periodic updates relating to the kit. You can choose not to receive these updates at any time. We will not sell or provide your email address to a third party.
  * We use Google Analytics to store information about your web browser, where you are from and which pages you visit in a Cookie. This helps us to improve the content for our visitors.

## Keeping Information Secure

Any data you provide to the site and is saved by us is stored securely in our database. Information you have provided is only available to HPI staff who require access to it for a specific job.

## Cookies

This website sets several cookies to store information on your computer. This allows us, amongst other things, to see which pages are most visited and where in the world our visitors are from.

We do not store any personally identifiable information in acookies, nor is this information ever provided to third parties apart from our analytics provider. It is only used by HPI Racing to help improve the content and services we offer to visitors of this website.

If you would rather we didn't set a cookie during your visit, you can adjust your web browser to prevent cookies being set by this website. Alternatively, you can indicate your preference below:

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

HPI Racing reserves the right to change this privacy policy as required. If we make changes to the Policy, will notify you by updating this page, so please revisit this page from time to time.

## Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit the HPI Racing website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of UK law.
